postpost.com 2013-05-23

# PostPost - Privacy policy

This privacy policy is applicable to the website located at http://postpost.com (the “Site”), which is operated by Boathouse Group Inc. or its affiliates or subsidiaries (“Boathouse” or “we”). Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites or to information that you may submit to us offline. PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEB SITE. Access to the Site is offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions and notices contained herein and in the Site’s Terms of Use. BY ACCESSING OR USING THIS SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THESE TERMS, DO NOT USE THIS SITE.

We do not share any personally identifiable information about you that we collect via the Site with third parties, except to companies that provide support services to us or perform functions on our behalf or in the other circumstances described in the “Use of Information” section below. Please review that section carefully for further details.

### MODIFICATION OF THESE TERMS.

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. When we do, the “Last Updated” line above will be revised. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of a changed Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the changes. Unless we provide you with specific notice, no changes to our Privacy Policy will apply retroactively.

### INFORMATION ABOUT YOU THAT WE MAY COLLECT.

Use of the Site or certain features of the Site may require registration and/or you may optionally choose to register to use the Site. For purposes of registration, we may collect and store certain personally identifiable information about you (“Personal Information”) such as your name, username, email address, . Additionally, we may also collect and store Personal Information when you use other features of the Site, submit comments or request more information, or otherwise communicate with us via the Site.

We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database.

When you interact with the Site, we may also collect certain non-Personal Information about you (“Anonymous Information”). For example, our servers may keep an activity log that tracks all visitors to the Site, including data such as the visitor’s IP address, registered domain or home server, time of access, date of access, web page(s) visited, number of clicks, software crash reports, type of browser used, session identification number, search terms, search results, access times and referring website’s addresses.

Like many websites, we use “cookies”, which are small text files that are stored on your computer or equipment when you visit certain online pages and that record your preferences. We may use cookies to track your use of our Site and its features. We may also use cookies to monitor traffic, improve the Site and make it easier and/or more relevant for your use.

Our Site is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age you should not use this Site, and under no circumstance should you send information about yourself to us.

While we use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, we will have no liability for disclosure of any information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties. No data storage system or transmission method can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and as a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you may supply.

### USE OF INFORMATION.

We may use the information we obtain from you to help us personalize and improve the Site and your experience on the Site; to communicate with you about the Site and products, services, and promotional offers; to update our records; to generally maintain your account with us, if any; and in connection with features offered on the Site that require information from you. We may also use your information to prevent or detect abuses of our Site or our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy and to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf. Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose Personal Information to any companies not affiliated with us.

We occasionally provide Personal Information to companies that provide support services to us or perform functions on our behalf, such as marketing, analytics, providing customer service, etc. These companies may need Personal Information in order to perform their functions. We do not authorize them to use the information we share with them for any other purpose.

We may also use or disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Site; (b) protect and defend the our rights or property, the Site or our users, and (c) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Site or the public.

We use Anonymous Information to help us determine how people use parts of the Site and who our users are so we can improve our Site. We may also use Anonymous Information to provide statistical information in aggregated form to our partners and other third parties about how our users collectively use Site. We may also use or share Anonymous Information (or other information, other than Personal Information) in any other manner that we decide is appropriate or necessary.

In the event of a sale of this Site or some or all of our business, we may disclose Personal Information to those involved in a transfer of all or part of the assets or business. If such an event were to occur, we would strive to ensure that the recipient treat your Personal Information as described in this policy.

### EXTERNAL SITES.

The Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet (the "External Sites"). Even if the External Site is operated by us or someone affiliated with us, this Privacy Policy does not apply to those sites.

### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION IN PUBLIC AREAS.

Any information you share in public areas, such as a “letting something go” balloon or any message boards or blogs, becomes public and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Please be careful about what you disclose, and do not post any Personal Information or any other information that you expect to keep private.

### APPLICABLE LAW.

The Web site is published in the United States and is subject to laws of the United States. If you are located in a country outside the United States and voluntarily submit personal information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States. We shall not be liable under any circumstances for damages resulting from use of information collected from visitors to the site. 

### CONTACT US.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or wish to correct or update any Personal Information that you have previously provided, please contact us as follows:

Boathouse Group Inc.  
Att’n: PostPost DMCA Legal Notice  
260 Charles Street  
Waltham, MA 02453

Copyright 2010 Boathouse. All rights reserved.
